

# **Zoran Janjic**

Nationality: Serbian | (+387) 644357829 | janjiczoran23@gmail.com |

https://github.com/ZoranUTF8 | https://zoran-janjic.netlify.app/ |

https://www.linkedin.com/in/janjiczoran/ Bosnia and Herzegovina

About me:

I am a motivated Junior full-stack developer with the ability to learn and collaborate in rapidly changing environments and compositions. Currently, working as a developer intern and getting working experience. Worked through 500+ hours of Bootcamp structure, learning JavaScript, Node.js, React.js and Java.

### WORK EXPERIENCE

04/2022 - CURRENT - Austria

## FULL-STACK DEVELOPER INTERN - BEEHIVVE

- Migrate a website from handlebars to React + Firebase.
- Stack: React.js, JavaScript, Firebase, Node.js, Express.js
- Optimize the web application for maximum speed and scalability.
- Build APIs and implement them in the application.
- Collaborate with backend engineers in ensuring technical feasibility .

09/2016 - 04/2021 - United Arab Emirates

#### **FLIGHT ATTENDANT - EMIRATES AIRLINES**

- Worked in English speaking environment and with multinational crews.
- Provide in-flight services to ensure that airline passengers have a comfortable and smooth flying experience and ensure the safety and satisfaction of passengers.
- Successfully work through any in-flight emergencies.

07/2012 - 02/2016 - United States

## SALES ASSOCIATE - ROYAL CARIBBEAN INTERNATIONAL

- Assist customers with the item selections and performed sales transactions.
- Promoted to Assistant Store Manager responsible for supporting the Store Manager in the daily business operation of a retail store.
- Contribute to daily sales by engaging sales to customers.

#### EDUCATION AND TRAINING

2021 - CURRENT

BS, COMPUTER SCIENCE - University of the People (Online)

12/2019 - 12/2020

JAVA DEVELOPER - ITAcademy by LINKgroup

### DIGITAL SKILLS

# **My Digital Skills**

HTML | CSS | JavaScript | React.js | Node.js | Express.js | Java | MySQL | NoSQL | Firebase | REST API | Git